http://www.rifftrax.com/privacy

Skip to main content
You own it!
Click to Play
Free US Domestic shipping at RiffTrax - all physical media is 10% off with select titles as low as $2.99!
Full Details here
Privacy Policy
You linked to this Privacy Policy via a product website owned by RiffTrax ("brand website"). This policy applies to all online communication with RiffTrax owned brands (known herein as “RiffTrax” or “Website”). When you provide RiffTrax with information through this Website, RiffTrax respects your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information RiffTrax collects about you during your visit and what RiffTrax does with that information. Please note that your use of the Website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.
At all times, RiffTrax reserves the right to disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; to protect RiffTrax rights or property (including without limitation in the event of a transfer of control of a RiffTrax company, affiliate, or brand, or substantially all of its assets), or during emergencies when safety is at risk, or for credit fraud protection and risk reduction purposes.
1. Information Collection and Use
We only collect personally identifiable information about you via this Website when you provide it in connection with a request for a product, service, or information. When you submit your personally identifiable information on this Website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
RiffTrax may use the information that you provide to fulfill your request for a product, information, or other service, or respond to an email or other request, as well as to create and deliver to you our newsletters or surveys, communications containing product information, usage tips or promotions, help improve our website(s) or services, or customize visitors' experience at our website(s). We do not share your credit card or other account information with unaffiliated third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities including, but not limited to, delivering a product or service that you order. If you prefer not to receive email marketing communications from us or from third parties, please see Section 3 below. You cannot opt-out of receiving communications from RiffTrax (or third parties who may assist us) relating to a specific order or request for a product or service. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.
We may also collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this Website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. Information gathered may be used in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may share or transfer such aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners.
In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation effective May 25th, 2018, we must disclose all personal data that is stored by RiffTrax or its agents and affiliates:
Email Address
A user’s email address is a necessary component of any user account, and it will be stored for the life of the account. The email address used to create the account is retained, as well as the user account’s currently active email address.
IP Address
IP Addresses can be stored temporarily as a basic function of the website in connection with security. An IP address which identifies a user’s shopping cart session is only retained for the lifetime of the session; however, when an order is finalized on our site, the associated IP address is retained with the order for potential security reasons.
Billing and Shipping Address
Whether it be digital or physical goods, a billing and shipping address will be temporarily stored as part of order fulfillment. This information is retained in reference to the associated order.
Payment Method
In connection with orders, RiffTrax collects payment method data. This data is not retained beyond what is necessary to complete a specific transaction unless you specifically opt to save your payment details as a future convenience. For your security, RiffTrax never records your complete, usable, payment method data; it is recorded on our behalf by our payment processor(s) in accordance with industry best practice, and a tokenized reference is stored on our servers. RiffTrax records this reference as necessary to complete transactions.
Cookies
This Website or one of its advertisers, affiliates, or sponsors may decide to collect data about on-site behavior during your session and your use of the sites of selected sponsors and advertisers through the use of "Cookies". Cookies are small computer files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive that allow websites to know how often someone visits a site and the activities they conduct while on that site (such as the chatrooms you visited, whether you submitted orders for products, etc.).
The information collected by cookies helps websites dynamically generate advertising and content on web pages or in e-mails specifically designed for you and also allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using RiffTrax.com and selected sponsors' and advertisers' sites, and for what purposes. RiffTrax may use cookie information to determine the popularity of certain content or advertisements.
Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject cookies, certain functions and conveniences of RiffTrax.com may not work properly. While it may be possible to link non-personal cookie information to Personal Information collected in other ways, we want you to know that if you accept our cookie we will not, without your consent, link the cookie information we collect to Personal Information you provide to us on our site.
Third Party Cookies
Sponsors, partners, advertisers, or affiliates on the site may also use their own cookies or web beacons when you click on their advertisement or link to their site or service, or even if the advertisement simply appears on a page or in an email that you are viewing. Some advertisers use companies to serve their ads and to monitor users' responses to ads, and these companies ("Ad Servers") may also collect non-personal information through the use of cookies or web beacons on our Website. In certain situations, information collection may be facilitated by momentarily directing your browser to the site of an Ad Server or other third party acting on behalf of the sponsor, partner, advertiser, or affiliate before redirecting your browser to its proper destination.
RiffTrax does not control these third parties' use of cookies or web beacons, or how they manage the non-personal information they gather through them. You should review the privacy policy of other sites you visit or link to from our site to understand how these other sites use cookies, and how they use the information they collect through the use of cookies or web beacons on their own sites. Certain Ad Servers allow you to prevent them from collecting data through the use of cookies. In order to do so, you must opt-out of such data collection with each individual site.
Collected Personal Data Not Listed In This Policy
In any instance RiffTrax or its agents collects personal data not listed in this Privacy Policy, such as during promotions, contests, surveys, participation will be in an opt-in basis. The use and retention of additional personal data will be disclosed in supplimentary Terms and Conditions of any such promotion, contest, or survey.
Content notice
This Website is intended for persons 13 years of age or older. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. However, if the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us at privacy@rifftrax.com if they want this information deleted from our files so that it is not in retrievable form. If we otherwise obtain knowledge that we have personally identifiable information about a child under 13 in retrievable form in our files, we will delete that information from our existing files so that it is not retrievable.
Removal of Personal Data
RiffTrax will remove collected personal data stored by RiffTrax and its agents, when a) the purpose for which it has been collected or otherwise processed has ended, or b) upon request of the data subject, with the exception of data we are required to retain by law. To request the removal of collected personal data, please contact us at privacy@rifftrax.com.
2. Ensuring Your Security
RiffTrax uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) TLS v3, an advanced security protocol that protects your credit card information and ensures secure online ordering. SSL Internet connections are encrypted, and thus protect all credit card ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number, so it cannot be read in transit. RiffTrax uses secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access, to safeguard your personal information.
3. Third Parties
RiffTrax relies on other companies and individuals to perform functions on behalf of RiffTrax. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, web hosting companies, and fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings). RiffTrax may share personally identifiable information with such third parties as appropriate for them to perform their functions, but they may not use such information for any other purpose.If you do not want to receive email marketing communications, see Section 5 below for opt-out information.
The Website may offer links to third party sites. This policy does not apply to third party websites or services not affiliated with or contracted by RiffTrax. Refer to the privacy policies of third party sites and services  to see how they collect and use this information.
4. Notification of Changes
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. RiffTrax may make changes at any time without notifying you. Periodically consult this Privacy Policy to stay up to date regarding how we use the information we collect.
5. Email Marketing
If you opt in to the RiffTrax Newsletter Service, RiffTrax may contact you via email correspondence. If for any reason you would no longer like to receive email messages from the RiffTrax brand you purchased, you can click on the “unsubscribe” link in the email footer, or visit our list manager web site at this link.
Your privacy is important to us, and for this reason RiffTrax will never sell or share your email address with any third parties for direct marketing purposes. Please note, if you decide not to receive marketing emails from RiffTrax, you may still receive “Transactional” email messages regarding your order (i.e. order confirmation, shipping information, customer service notifications, etc.) If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at support@rifftrax.com.
6. Notification of Data Breaches
In the event that user data is revealed to parties not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy, RiffTrax will notify you via your primary contact email address of the data breach within 72 hours of becoming aware of the data breach. RiffTrax also notifies relevant authorities of data breaches as required by law.
Last updated: May 24, 11:25 AM
Deals of the Week: $2 OFF!
Jack Frost - on sale now!
Deal expires 9:16am PST December 14, 2020
MST3K: Red Zone Cuba - on sale now!
Deal expires 9:10am PST December 16, 2020
Indiana Jones and the Kingdom Of The Crystal Skull - on sale now!
Deal expires 9:00am PST December 11, 2020
View all current offers
This website uses cookies as described in our Privacy Policy
Got it!
